yunio.com 2014-07-15

# Yunio - Cloud Storage for Everyone

## Yunio Privacy Policy

Your privacy is of vital importance to Yunio. So, please carefully read our privacy policy, describing how we collect, use, disclose, assign and save your information. Should you have any questions, please let us know.

### Collection and Use of Personal Information

Personal information refers to data that is solely used for the purposes of identifying or contacting someone. You may be required to give your personal information during your contact with Yunio. Yunio shall use the information according to the Privacy Policy and may integrate with other information for the purposes of providing and improving our products, service, content and advertising. 

### What Personal Information Do We Collect

We collect diversified information when you creation of a Yunio account, validate your email, purchase value-added services, download updated software or participate in online questionnaires, which may include your name, mailing address, phone number, email address, preferred contact information, online payment information and credit card information. 

When you share your content with your family or friends via Yunio, send gift coupons or invitations, Yunio will also collect information that you provide regarding those people, such as name, mailing address, email address and phone number.

### How Do We Use Your Personal Information

We timely inform you of latest product launches, software updates and event forecasting based on personal information collected. The information will also help us to improve, better develop and deliver our products, services, content and advertising. You may tell us at any time if you don't intend to be included in our mailing list.

From time to time, we will use your personal information to make sure you receive important notices, e.g. communication for purchases, changes to our terms of service, conditions and policies, etc. You are subject to this communication since the information is important to your usage and experience of using our product.

We will also use the personal information for audits, data analyses and studies as well as other internal purposes, as to continually improve Yunio products, services and communication with users. 

We will use your information to manage any raffles or give-aways, competitions or similar promotional activities that you will participate in.

### Collection and Use of Non-personal Information

We will also collect non-personal information that is not directly related to a particular person. We may collect, use, assign and disclose non-personal information for any purpose. The following are some examples of non-personal information that we may collect and how we may use this information. 

We will collect information including occupation, language, postal code, zip code, unique equipment identification code, location and time zones where Yunio products are located and in use, so that we may better understand our users' behavior, for the purposes of improving our products, services and advertising.

We will also collect information in connection with activities performed by users on our website, Windows / (Mac) OS X / Linux / Unix and other desktop client terminals as well as iOS / Android / Windows Phone and other mobile platform client terminals, and information obtained from other products and services. We will summarize the information to help us in providing more helpful information to our users and understanding what is our users' interests in our website, products and services. The summarized data shall be regarded as non-personal information with regard to the Privacy Policy. 

All personal and non-personal information shall be deemed as personal information once combined or integrated.

### Cookies and Other Technologies

"Cookies" and other technologies may be adopted for the Yunio website, online services, interactive application programs, email messages and advertising, e.g. pixel tags and web beacon. These technologies help us to better understand our users' behavior and tell us what has been browsed on our website, as well as help us to improve and measure advertising efficiency and web searches. Information collected by means of cookies and other technologies is considered as non-personal information. However, the same identification will be deemed as personal information provided that IP addresses or similar identification markings are personal information in accordance with local laws. Similarly, integrated or combined personal and non-personal information shall be deemed as personal information for the purposes of the Privacy Policy.

Yunio adopts cookies and technologies in mobile advertising services and partners thereof to apply advertisements that you may be interested in, to measure the efficiency of these advertisements and to manage the number of times they are used.

During your access to our website, online services and application programs, Yunio and our partners will remember your personal information by means of cookies and other technologies. In these cases, we aim to make your experience more convenient and customized. For instance, with your name, we will be able to deliver our welcome to you when you revisit the Yunio website. Acknowledgement of your country and language (and your school if you are an educator) will help use to provide you with customized and more helpful shopping experiences. Acknowledgement of some product purchased or some services applied via your computer or device will help us in sending you more proper advertisement and email communication that you may find interesting. Acknowledgement of your contact information and that of your computer or device will help us in registering products purchased by you, making your operating system more customized, establishing your services and delivering better customer services to you.

When you intend to disable cookies and you are using Internet Explorer web browser, please select preference option under Internet Explorer, then select security option and disable cookies. For Yunio mobile devices, please select setting option, then browser and finally Cookies. In case of other browsers, please ask your provider how to disable cookies. Please note that some functions attached to Yunio website will become unavailable when Cookies are disabled. Similar to most websites, Yunio.com automatically collects some information and saves the same in a history file, including IP address, type of browser and language, Internet Service Provider (ISP), indication page, exit page, operating system, date/time marking and click stream data. We use the information to understand and analyze trends, manage website, understand users' behavior on website and collect population statistics information of the entire user group. Yunio may use the information for marketing and advertising services.

"Click-through URL" linked to our Yunio website is adopted in some of our emails. When one click-through URL is selected, it will go through an independent web server before coming to our target page. Our tracking of such click-through data will help us in determining users' interests in some topics and in measuring the efficiency of our communication with users. 

Pixel tags allow us to send emails with a readable format and lets us know whether the email has been viewed. With this information, we can reduce the number of emails sent to our users.

### Disclosure to Third Parties

In some cases, Yunio will provide some personal information to strategic partners cooperating with Yunio in product and service supplies or helping Yunio in customer marketing. For instance, your downloading and initiation of your Yunio iOS client gives Yunio authorization to communicate information provided during such initiation, so as to facilitate the delivery of our services. When you are permitted to use the services, your account will be applicable to privacy policies of Yunio and operators thereof. Yunio will only share the personal information with any third party solely for the purposes of supplying or improving our products, services and advertising, other than marketing purposes of the third party.

### Internet Service Provider

Yunio will share personal information with companies that provide information processing, reinforce customer data, assess your interest in our products and services as well as performs customer surveys or satisfaction surveys. These companies are obligated to protect your information and maintain its privacy at any juncture where Yunio conducts business.

### Miscellaneous 

Yunio may disclose your personal information when necessary in accordance with laws, legal proceedings, actions and/or requirements raised by public institutions and government authorities inside or outside your country of residence. We may disclose your information provided that we believe that such disclosure is mandatory or proper in the regard of state security, law enforcement or other matters of public importance.

We may disclose your information provided that we believe that such disclosure is reasonable and mandatory for the purpose of executing our terms of service and conditions or protecting our business or users. In addition, we may assign all personal information collected to a third party in case of reorganization, merger, acquisition or sale of our assets.

### Protection of Personal Information

Yunio will take all precautions including administrative, technical and practical measures to safeguard your personal information from losing, misappropriating and misusing as well as unauthorized reference, disclosure, change or destruction. Please adopt Security Socket Layer (SSL) encryption technology for all websites collecting personal information during your application of Yunio website. You have to use an SSL-supporting browser such as Safari, Firefox or Internet Explorer during your purchase of the product. This allows the protection of your confidentiality and of your personal information when the data is transmitted through the Internet. When you apply Yunio products, services or application programs or post messages on Yunio forum, chat room or social networking services, personal information shared by you will be seen by and available to other users. You shall be solely responsible for the personal information you decide to submit in the foregoing case. For instance, your name and email address publicized in the forum will become public.

### Access to Personal Information

Visiting and updating your personal information on our main website is the most convenient way for you to help us ensure the accuracy and completeness of your contact information and preferences when you log into your account. We will in good faith make an honest endeavor to allow you to access your personal information, so that you can request to correct or delete any inaccurate data not to be maintained by Yunio in accordance with laws or for legal business purposes. We have the right to refuse any unreasonable repetitive requests, ones that may be inappropriate, damaging to others' privacy, extremely unrealistic or requests for the right to access information not required in accordance with local laws. Any requests for information access, information correction or deletion can be sent to regional privacy contact list.

### Children

We will not, to the best of our knowledge, collect personal information of someone whose age is below thirteen. We will take actions to delete user information of anyone who is below thirteen years of age as soon as possible upon discovery.

### Third-party Website and Service

Yunio's websites, products, application programs and services may be linked to any third-party websites, products and services. Our products and services may be derived from other third-party products or services, e.g. third-party Yunio application programs. Information collected by any third party, including location data or contact information, shall be subject to privacy policies of the third party. We encourage you to read and better understand third-party privacy policies.

### Our Commitment to Your Privacy

To ensure the safety of your personal information, we inform all Yunio employees of our corporate privacy and safety guidelines and internally have protection measures strictly implemented.

### Privacy 

Should you have any questions regarding Yunio's privacy policy, please feel free to contact us.

Yunio may revise its privacy policy from time to time and will post the most current version on our website.

509 Caobao Road, Suite 406, XinCaoHeJing Building, Xuhui District, Shanghai, China. 200233

Last updated: April 3rd, 2014
